235 S. Buckhout St. State College, PA 16801 (484) 904-2099

HIGHLIGHTS

Dual major student at Penn State with concentrations in computer architecture and solid state engineering with research experience in semiconductor fabrication process and design for test methodologies. Previously worked at Penn State ARL developing intelligence applications for data ingest and visualization resulting in an active US Secret clearance and at IBM developing Logic Built in Self Test (LBIST) routines for Z series processors on a new test platform with a flexible object oriented interface.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, C, C++, C#, x86 Assembly, MIPS Assembly Scripting Languages: Python, MATLAB, Shell (Bash), Perl, PHP, Batch Design Tools: Cadence Virtuoso, Autodesk EAGLE, KiCAD, NI Multisim

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science Computer Engineering, Electrical Engineering
The Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA
May 2019
College of Engineering & Schreyer Honors College
Majors: Computer Engineering, Electrical Engineering
GPA: 3.53/4.00

EXPERIENCE

Design for Test and Characterization Intern

May 2018 - Present

- IBM, z/Systems, Poughkeepsie, NY
 - Assisted in migration from single use Perl scripts to object oriented Python
 - Assisted in development of new chip test platform based on Kintex Ultrascale
 - Developed CP Logic Built in Self Test routines that ran 40% faster than before
 - Developed interactive testing and visualization platform for characterization
 - Identified potential 10% reduction in dynamic power of latches for z/CP

Relevant Skills: Python, Jupyter, SQL, Neo4j, Cypher Query, VLSI, VHDL, BIST

Visualization Intern

May 2017 - May 2018

The Pennsylvania State University ARL, SEALab, University Park, PA

- Supported development for existing visualization applications in an Agile team
- Parallelized physics simulation and rendering engines on existing application
- Resolved race conditions in scene graph of rendering engine for CAVEs
- Developed several new data pipelines for databases, blockchains and Excel

Relevant Skills: Java, OpenGL, C, SQL, SQLite, Apache Tomcat, Unity 3D, C# Other Information: Active US Secret Clearance

Projects

4KB SRAM Cache

Fall 2018

The Pennsylvania State University, CMPEN/EE 416

- Worked with partner to develop 4KB SRAM Cache using 200nm TSMC process
- Developed Python tools to optimize path length & transistor sizing
- Completed schematic, layout, and simulation using HSPICE

Relevant Skills: VLSI, Cadence Virtuoso, Computer Architecture, Python

Wristband Scanner

Spring 2018 - Present

The Pennsylvania State University, HackPSU

- Worked with a team of several other students to develop an IOT scanner
- Developed C++ abstractions for Arduino to interface with RFID scanner chips
- Developing PCB design with multiple micro-controllers and planar antennae

Relevant Skills: C++, Arduino, PCB Design, Antenna Design